[{"npcName":"%男主角%","standFront":"1_hero_stand_front","emotionSatisfied":"","body":"1_male","maxStep":8,"minStandTime":3,"npcId":1,"vy":0.3,"emotionWalking":"","vx":0.6,"walkBack":"1_hero_walk_back","standBack":"1_hero_stand_back","emotionRejected":"","head":"1_male_head","minStep":5,"maxStandTime":8,"walkFront":"1_hero_walk_front"},{"npcName":"%女主角%","standFront":"2_heroine_stand_front","emotionSatisfied":"","body":"2_female","maxStep":8,"minStandTime":3,"npcId":2,"vy":0.3,"emotionWalking":"","vx":0.6,"walkBack":"2_heroine_walk_back","standBack":"2_heroine_stand_back","emotionRejected":"","head":"2_female_head","minStep":5,"maxStandTime":8,"walkFront":"2_heroine_walk_front"},{"npcName":"精灵村长","standFront":"3_ermo_stand_front","emotionSatisfied":"love","body":"3_ermo","maxStep":8,"minStandTime":5,"npcId":3,"vy":0.1,"emotionWalking":"smile","vx":0.2,"walkBack":"3_ermo_walk_back","standBack":"3_ermo_stand_back","emotionRejected":"surprise","head":"3_ermo_head","minStep":3,"maxStandTime":8,"walkFront":"3_ermo_walk_front"},{"npcName":"侏儒奇姆","standFront":"4_chimu_stand_front","emotionSatisfied":"slobber","body":"4_chimu","maxStep":8,"minStandTime":3,"npcId":4,"vy":0.2,"emotionWalking":"cool","vx":0.4,"walkBack":"4_chimu_walk_back","standBack":"4_chimu_stand_back","emotionRejected":"burn","head":"4_chimu_head","minStep":4,"maxStandTime":8,"walkFront":"4_chimu_walk_front"},{"npcName":"侏儒蒂姆","standFront":"5_timu_stand_front","emotionSatisfied":"slobber","body":"5_timu","maxStep":8,"minStandTime":3,"npcId":5,"vy":0.2,"emotionWalking":"cool","vx":0.4,"walkBack":"5_timu_walk_back","standBack":"5_timu_stand_back","emotionRejected":"vomit","head":"5_timu_head","minStep":4,"maxStandTime":8,"walkFront":"5_timu_walk_front"},{"npcName":"皮克希","standFront":"6_widine_stand_front","emotionSatisfied":"miao","body":"6_widine","maxStep":8,"minStandTime":3,"npcId":6,"vy":0.4,"emotionWalking":"prettiness","vx":0.8,"walkBack":"6_widine_walk_back","standBack":"6_widine_stand_back","emotionRejected":"anger","head":"6_widine_head","minStep":5,"maxStandTime":8,"walkFront":"6_widine_walk_front"},{"npcName":"汪汪唐","standFront":"7_tst_stand_front","emotionSatisfied":"shout","body":"7_tst","maxStep":8,"minStandTime":3,"npcId":7,"vy":0.4,"emotionWalking":"question","vx":0.8,"walkBack":"7_tst_walk_back","standBack":"7_tst_stand_back","emotionRejected":"spook","head":"7_tst_head","minStep":5,"maxStandTime":8,"walkFront":"7_tst_walk_front"},{"npcName":"矮人金雳","standFront":"8_gimli_stand_front","emotionSatisfied":"shout","body":"8_gimli","maxStep":8,"minStandTime":3,"npcId":8,"vy":0.2,"emotionWalking":"smile","vx":0.4,"walkBack":"8_gimli_walk_back","standBack":"8_gimli_stand_back","emotionRejected":"grimace","head":"8_gimli_head","minStep":3,"maxStandTime":8,"walkFront":"8_gimli_walk_front"},{"npcName":"小熊","standFront":"9_jaina_stand_front","emotionSatisfied":"love","body":"9_jaina","maxStep":8,"minStandTime":3,"npcId":9,"vy":0.3,"emotionWalking":"sweat","vx":0.6,"walkBack":"9_jaina_walk_back","standBack":"9_jaina_stand_back","emotionRejected":"startle","head":"9_jaina_head","minStep":3,"maxStandTime":8,"walkFront":"9_jaina_walk_front"},{"npcName":"希尔芙","standFront":"10_sylph_stand_front","emotionSatisfied":"miao","body":"10_sylph","maxStep":8,"minStandTime":3,"npcId":10,"vy":0.3,"emotionWalking":"prettiness","vx":0.6,"walkBack":"10_sylph_walk_back","standBack":"10_sylph_stand_back","emotionRejected":"fire","head":"10_sylph_head","minStep":3,"maxStandTime":8,"walkFront":"10_sylph_walk_front"}]